



## **Christos Kaitanidis**

O Home: 41335, Larisa, Greece

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin/in/kaitanidis

Date of birth: 4 Jan 1981 Nationality: Greek

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a professional IT engineer with ten years of experience in IT support, working for the Hellenic Goverment, Ministry of Education. I have also worked as a Computer Science teacher in secondary grade education in Greece for seven years. Now, I am looking for new exciting projects along with my current occupational status, in part time and remote working.

In my personal life i live in Larisa and i am father of four children.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[ 14 Mar 2018 – Current ]

## Chief of Information Department in Directorate of Secondary Education in Larisa

Ministry of Education <a href="https://dide.lar.sch.gr/site/">https://dide.lar.sch.gr/site/</a>

**Business or sector:** Information and communication

IT support for all Schools and Departments of Directorate of Secondary Education in Larisa.

[ 31 Oct 2013 – 13 Mar 2018 ]

## IT engineer of Information Department in Directorate of Secondary Education in Larisa

Ministry of Education <a href="https://dide.lar.sch.gr/site/">https://dide.lar.sch.gr/site/</a>

**Business or sector:** Information and communication IT support of Directorate of Secondary Education in Larisa.

31 Aug 2006 - 30 Oct 2013]

## **Computer Science Teacher in Secondary Education**

## **Ministry of Education**

Teaching Computer Science in schools of Secondary Education.

16 Dec 2003 – 29 Apr 2005

# IT engineer of E-Learning Department in Computer Technology Institute and Press "Diophantus"

Computer Technology Institute and Press "Diophantus" https://www.cti.gr/en/

Worked as a Computer engineer on projects "e-Omogeneia" and "ΤΣ-Εκπαιδευτικό Υλικό", mainly supporting the portals of the aforementioned projects in PHP and ASP.Net technologies.

30 Jun 2003 – 30 Aug 2003 ]

## IT engineer

**DEI** www.dei.gr

**Business or sector:** Electricity, gas, steam and air conditioning supply IT support of Departments of DEI Patras.

31 Dec 2002 - 29 Jun 2003 ]

### Options G.P.

Programmer in projects for ATE bank and Vodafone, Java and Oracle programming technologies. Also, author of various e-Commerce oriented online articles about Digital Watermarking, Business Intelligence, Knowledge Management and Process Automation, Mobile-commerce etc.

## [ Current ] Adults Education

#### **EKDDA** and **DIEK**

City: Larisa and Patra Country: Greece

-Teaching Computer Science and Digital Skills

In various occasions, since 2003.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

[ 16 Jul 2008 ]

## **Masters diploma in Computer Science and Technology**

University of Patras, Computer Engineering and Information department https://www.ceid.upatras.gr/en

City: Patra Country: Greece

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

Final grade: Excellent Level in EQF: EQF level 7

**NQF Level:** Masters Diploma **Type of credits:** ECTS **Number of credits:** 120

**Thesis:** Semantic Web and Personalization in Searching and Crawling Link: https://nemertes.library.upatras.gr/jspui/handle/10889/967

30 Sep 1998 – 29 Jul 2003 ]

## **Diploma in Computer Science**

University of Patras, Computer Engineering and Information department https://www.ceid.upatras.gr/en

City: Patra Country: Greece

Field(s) of study: Information and Communication Technologies

Final grade: 7.74 out of 10 Level in EQF: EQF level 7

**NQF Level:** Integrated Master **Type of credits:** ECTS **Number of credits:** 300

Thesis: Διαχείριση μεγάλων κοινοπρακτικών δανείων ΑΤΕ

# [ 29 Jun 1998 ] High School Diploma

## 1st General Highschool of Katerini

City: Katerini Country: Greece

Field(s) of study: Education

Final grade: 19 and 7/10 out of 20 Level in EQF: EQF level 4

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Greek

### Other language(s):

## **English**

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1** 

#### German

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING A1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

#### **Soft Skills**

Leadership | Critical thinking | Decision-making | Collaboration and teamwork | Em pathic listener | Reliability | Responsibility | Conflict resolution | Organizational and planning skills | Research and analytical skills

#### **Hard Skills**

HTML5/CSS, Javascript | XML | Programming Languages: Java, C, Kotlin, C#, Javascript | Database (MySQL/phpMyAdmin, SQL Server) | PHP | C,C++, C# | Python | Linux/ Linux Server | React Coding | Android Development (Kotlin, Java) | ASP.NET | PLESK + CPanel Administration | WordPress, Joomla | Microsoft SC-900 | Microsoft SC-300 | Microsoft SC-400 | Microsoft AZ-104 | Microsoft AZ-500 | Azure Fundamentals | Microsoft Office | Google Cloud Services (Gmail, Google Drive, Google Docs, Google Sheets, Google Forms) | GIMP 2.0 (Experienced) | Knowledge and use of Adobe Photoshop

#### **DRIVING LICENCE**

Cars: B

## **CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS**

## Many Seminars and Conferences mentioned below

Coaching και Mentoring, e-Government, Administration of Linux Server, CCNA, Leadership Startegic Thinking and Organizational Changes, Digital Transformation in Education, Open Data, DPO and ICT Security and more... Lifelong Learning

## **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

[ 23 Nov 2005 ] **Honours award Awarding institution:** Technical Chamber of Greece (TEE-TCG)

Award for my excellent performance in my studies for my Computer Science Diploma during 2002-2003.

## **HOBBIES AND IN-TERESTS**

#### Chess

Love the game, the tension and the competition.

I love to play basketball, always playing for the team, as a point guard.

## Guitar

Playing a little for myself and family.

## **Agriculture**

I spend time in general agriculture, taking care of my plants and a few dozens of olive trees i own.